To Catch a Killer is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Eric Till.
"To Catch a Killer" tells the true gruesome story of John Wayne Gacy - a good friend and helpful neighbour, a great child
entertainer, a respectful businessman, and a violent serial killer who raped and murdered over 30 young boys.
John Wayne Gacy, played by Brian Dennehy.
Joe 'Polock' Kozenczak, played by Michael Riley.
Rachel Grayson, played by Margot Kidder.
Linda Carlson, played by Meg Foster.
Ted Koslo, played by Martin Julien.
Mike Paxton, played by Scott Hylands.
To Catch a Killer is a two-part television film from 1992, directed by
Eric Till and starring Brian Dennehy and Michael Riley.
It is based on the true story of the pursuit of
American serial killer John Wayne Gacy.
The film explores themes of handcuffs, biography, serial killer, sadist.
The tone is intense and dark and emotional.